Anjali Mishra anjalimarch24@gmail.com Flat 206 TNR Vaishnovi Apartment, Hyderabad, India

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Over 6 years of experience in Information Technology, with a specialization in Software Quality Assurance Testing. Extremely methodical, Hardworking, driven, and motivated Quality Assurance Engineer having expertise in functional testing as well as in automating web applications. Advanced background in anticipating user behaviors and providing the solution to improve product quality for various software applications.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Consultant

Jun 2021 - Present

Deloitte Consulting India Private Limited, Hyderabad, India • Hyderabad, India

- Drafted Test Plan which included testing objectives, testing phases, scenarios, and test environment after a thorough analysis of the business rules.
- Involved in test cases review by the development team, and product management and modified the test cases based on their feedback.
- Responsible for planning, executing, and managing the UI automation scripts for AngularJS applications using Webdriver IO and Mocha Testing Framework.
- Created and enhanced numerous test scripts to handle changes in the objects and to provide better regression test coverage.
- Created manual test cases, and reviewed with different stakeholders to validate the functionality, so that it meets the expected business criteria.
- Performed functional testing to identify various critical points in the application.
- Performed Webservices testing using Rest Assured to reduce manual effort.
- Participated in meetings, and teleconferences walk-through with the development team, QA manager, and Project manager (PM).
- Coordinated with technical support associates to fix proprietary software issues to provide the best solution at the earliest.
- Verified, edited, and updated test data in new or existing systems before testing the software to meet the peculiar changes in enhancements.

Consultant

Jun 2018 - Jun 2021

1/8/23, 8:38 PM Resume: Miss - Job Bank

Deloitte Consulting India Private Limited, Hyderabad, India • Hyderabad, India

- Participated in requirement understanding and developing usecases.
- Drafted functional scenarios and testcases to provided better coverage of the functional requirements and reviewed with team lead.
- Shared test reports with various test metrics with team members and team lead, to have a clarity on quality control.
- Automated functional testcases by using Selenium Web-Driver and TestNG testing tools.
- Developed scripts for data driven framework using Selenium WebDriver, TestNG and Apache POI API.
- Used Maven to build and run the Selenium automation framework shared consolidated automation test reports.

Software Testing Engineer

Apr 2016 - Jun 2018 Cybage Software • Hyderabad

- Participated in all phases of Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC), its methodologies such as Agile, SCRUM.
- Involved in understanding the business requirements of the customer and developed testcases.
- Developed, modified, and executed scripts.
- Developed new Pages as per the software application.
- Implemented Generic Functions and Project specific Functions in Libraries, in Automation test framework built using Page Object Model design pattern.
- Customized scripts using parameterization techniques.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Technology

Jul 2004 - Jul 2008

Dr. A.P.J. Abdul Kalam Technical University • Lucknow

- Completed my degree in Computer Science and Engineering.
- Learned programming languages such as, Java and explored various web technology tools.
- Participated in testing college web portal.

SKILLS

Software Testing: Functional Testing, Automation Testing

1/8/23, 8:38 PM Resume: Miss - Job Bank

- Testing Framework: TestNG, Jasmine, Mocha, Cucumber
- Desing Patterns: Page Object Model, Behaviour Driven Development
- Functional Testing Tool: Selenium WebDriver/Grid, Protractor, Webdriver IO, Cypress
- API Testing Tool: Rest Assured
- Technologies/Domain: US Tax Process, Hospitality, Fleet Management System
- Programming Languages: Java, JavaScript, Apache POI
- Web Technologies: Angular JS, Node.JS
- Scripting: Java, JavaScript
- IDE: Eclipse, VS Code
- Testing Framework: TestNG, Jasmine, Mocha
- Web Debugging Tool: XPath, Firepath, Firebug
- Build Tool: Maven
- Processes: Agile-Scrum, Waterfall
- Bug Tracking Tools: JIRA, VSTS, QTest
- Continuous Integration Tools: Jenkins, Azure Devops
- Version Control: GIT
- DataBase: SQL Server
- Operating Systems: Windows

PROFESSIONAL CREDENTIALS

ISTQB Certified Tester Foundation Level

World Education Services: Educational Credential Assessment for Immigration, Refugees and Canada

VOLUNTEER WORK

Impact Day Volunteer

Jun 2018 - Dec 2022

Deloitte Consulting India Private Limited • Hyderabad

- Recorded Braille books as part of Deloitte Impact Day programme.
- Have taken classes in an Agape international as part of Deloitte Impact Day programme.

LGBTQ Ally

Jun 2018 - Jan 2022

Deloitte Consulting India Private Limited • Hyderabad, India

• LGBTQ Ally and participated in various sessions across firm to help and support community.

1/8/23, 8:38 PM Resume: Miss - Job Bank

AWARDS AND HONOURS

Applause Award

2022

• Got Applause award for automating MyInsight CE using Webdriver IO.

Innovation Champion Award

2021

• Got recognized for building a proof of concept for automating webservices using Rest Assured.

Spot Award

2019

• Got recognized for automating MyInsight CE using protractor tool.

Spot Award

2022

• Got recognized with spot award for delivering the essential test metrics and providing support to peers and new hires.